[SPEAKER_00]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, how are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: End of the day, finally.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, still like a lunchtime for me, but good to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where are you based?
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right now, me and my wife, we're in Sao Paulo, but we're just doing the whole moving out, closing off stuff to go to Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not sure how much you know about my story, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: yeah i mean like uh i only know that like dmitry said that like you spoke he spoke with you and he said like it would be great for me to speak with you also and i saw a few comments from him okay but there weren't anything related to the location where you live etc anyway okay okay i can explain we will go there we will go there anyway uh so i'm going to see you here uh first of all um
[SPEAKER_01]: As I understood, again, confirm, please, if you can.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you used to be, let's say, like a full-stack developer, software engineer, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then at some point, you decided to kind of change something and just started to do something AI-related, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a mix of the hype plus the already existing interest on the sci-fi topic of artificial intelligence.
[SPEAKER_01]: here we are it's also a very demanded kind of position yeah i see you know like i had a call with i forgot his name oh yeah uh so with another guy this morning and uh he said to me that like it's kind of similar situation he used to be for years like software engineer then
[SPEAKER_01]: tech leader than CTO even and then he decided to kind of to step back and start to like from the be like and be as an AI engineer yeah and the main reason for him was because he realized that like
[SPEAKER_01]: the people who just writes code it's not kind of we don't need anymore those right yeah and then it's like a change from the i would say like a speech move like transforming sorry it's like end of the day anyway so it's like transforming from the software engineer into the product engineer and it's like completely change on the way how we work and how we do stuff okay
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, let me do the small intro, and then I would propose for you to do the small intro, like super small.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let us maybe go deeper into a few topics.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would ask some questions, then you would ask a few questions, and then we will see where we are.
[SPEAKER_01]: OK?
[SPEAKER_01]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so cool my name is evil usually I live in Berlin for the Years almost but I just arrived to Portugal Yeah, every year I'm here because I'm surfing so that's why like every year like approximately in Stuff like in January February March.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there I come here to surf nice waves.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everything is good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't been here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I
[SPEAKER_00]: yeah i actually was living in portugal i have friends there i can tell you a bit more later okay i see i see cool uh you speak portuguese i guess i don't speak portuguese i don't speak but i try to learn it's not the easiest language i would say okay anyway um yeah so
[SPEAKER_01]: for you to know who I am, what is my background, and for you to be easier to explain yourself.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I used to be a designer, then head of design, then I was a part of the startup incubator.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was a co-founder of the startup incubator together with my partner.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were a team of five people, then in one year we became 120, and then more and more.
[SPEAKER_01]: then it was like a not huge but pretty big startup incubator with hundreds of startups that went through us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Different topics, different things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say most of them failed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a startup, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it seems to be true.
[SPEAKER_01]: But a few of them, exactly, a few of them actually survived.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then at some point, like after five years working there, I switch
[SPEAKER_01]: been similar to Phenom and I was a CPO there for five years.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I moved here and I lived in Berlin and we started this like Phenom thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm one of the founders of Phenom.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm from the game and also five years, I don't know, like every five years I change something.
[SPEAKER_01]: So for five years I was a CTO here in Finland.
[SPEAKER_01]: And after this time, you know, like I'm usually the guy who goes from zero to one, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a product, we have a bunch of customers, we have 700 employees approximately.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I decided that it's a time for me to move on, to move on to the next step.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we brought Christian.
[SPEAKER_01]: Christian is our CPO.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he runs basically from one to many.
[SPEAKER_01]: So his task is to scale the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not an easy task, I would say.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I started to lead a kind of crazy project.
[SPEAKER_01]: It wasn't AI at the first, because, like, you know, like two years, somebody cared about AI.
[SPEAKER_01]: So as much as today, people are thinking about AI, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then at some point, yeah, now we have a team with the engineers, managers, who knows, and go into AI, and me, who runs the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: is how we work on the AI in companies.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we have three pillars, I would call it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The one is to basically to bring operation excellence.
[SPEAKER_01]: It means that like all the ops things in ops team, customer care, sales, I don't know, you name it, like we have a lot of different process stuff to optimize.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the most important, I would call it, it's bad to say so, but
[SPEAKER_01]: our job is to eliminate or replace the people in the machines, let's call it this way.
[SPEAKER_01]: The less people company has, the better, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: We even have a metric that's called FTE per active customer, so it means that how many kind of
[SPEAKER_01]: So the second direction, or stream, or pillar, whatever, name it, it's AI-based users.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're working on different products, features, and some of those products are AI-native or AI-first.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for example, we have AI accounting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, probably in your country it's like kind of the same, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: So, when you're doing the taxes, you... Oh yeah, I have a company, my company here, I'm a client of them, same as you guys are for your clients.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's called Contact Lizzy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's tax advising basically, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So and we decided to replace people again.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we eliminated tax advisors completely and automate the whole thing and the whole process also from the tax preparation to submitting to the tax authorities.
[SPEAKER_01]: We started with the German market and it's working.
[SPEAKER_01]: So now we are moving to the France market, French market, and then we'll see how it goes further.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's AI system that works across the whole product.
[SPEAKER_01]: And instead of just being as a kind of support assistant, we decided to go deeper and, I don't know, keep in mind the experience similar to OpenCore, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you checked it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you tried OpenCore?
[SPEAKER_01]: OpenCore, yeah, yeah, sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so you talk to him and he goes do stuff and he comes back to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah I got some Russian.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes Cyrillic Yeah, I'm originally from Bulgaria by the way, I do speak Russian but like I'm Bulgarian I think I saw something on your link, it didn't go out Yeah anyway, um
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and the goal here is to create an AI system that would be proactive, completely proactive.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not like the way when the customer asks something like, hey, how to issue the card?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then it goes, to issue your card, please go here.
[SPEAKER_01]: here and there, but instead, just issue the card.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is the goal, to work when the customers say, get shit done, and to be proactive as much as possible, to provide insights, things to the user to do, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is what we are working on now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not released yet, but this is where we're looking for people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've read about some AI accountant feature that you guys were releasing from last year to September or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was official.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that the one that you're mentioning with the proactive text filings or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've read some stuff about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So tell me about yourself.
[SPEAKER_00]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do have some points on the things you mentioned, but I was waiting for you to finish of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: From my side, yeah, Felipe, I am Brazilian, I was actually a psychologist by graduation, I'm not sure if you saw that on my CV, but I was a shrink for like five years, you know, people would lay down on my sofa and talk about their lives and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really nice and, yeah, it was my desired profession.
[SPEAKER_00]: But of course, when I was starting to go through my adult life, I also was a tech boy since I was 12 years old.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was selling Game Boy games in diskettes, in three diskettes zipped in parts.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, it was all over myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: So when I came to Sao Paulo, which is a big metropolis in Brazil, then finding a tech job was very easy for whoever can do the job.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was already nine years ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I started to do frontend, TypeScript, AWS and bits and bits here and there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so I love the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, you can do so much.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can spread yourself a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was very different from
[SPEAKER_00]: being a psychologist, of course, and at some point I got a job offer to go to the Netherlands to be a software engineer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, it's easier to go as a software engineer than to go as a psychologist.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it just became my professional from the day, from night to day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you miss it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you miss it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I miss the process of being in a personal life investigation and being a nobody inside the room so the person can open themselves and explore stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: But to be honest, I do parts of that with people around me, friends, but also I brought some of those capabilities to my actual job.
[SPEAKER_00]: And hopefully with AI, that is even more, even deeper what I can do with this basic knowledge.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because right now we talk about hallucinations, memory and bias and so on.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's all about psychology as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I can get there.
[SPEAKER_00]: But so when I got to the Netherlands, I was starting to look what I'm going to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: I worked in this more established company called Schubert Filies, which is a consultancy technology company.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I was doing most of it was data engineering.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was participating in two projects, customer facing, but also internal.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at some point, they were just too conservative for my preference.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I started to look outside and then I went to blockchain conferences.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love the topic.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it was the...
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I'm going to interrupt you from time to time.
[SPEAKER_01]: You said they were too conservative for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you mean by that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, basically, they didn't want to...
[SPEAKER_00]: you know, consider changing the technologies, you know, to move forward with the technology simply because it was working and the client was not asking for anything anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm very tech savvy, let's say.
[SPEAKER_00]: So for me, it's like, OK, I know it's working, but we keep on
[SPEAKER_00]: you know, putting fire out because one bit or another fails and then we fix because we don't have a more robust solution.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have some kind of a gadgetry thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was not satisfied with that and I felt like I was not doing
[SPEAKER_00]: much with my capabilities.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like to learn things by myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did this to learn technology.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I was kind of like sitting on the sofa and being there.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was very sad to leave the company.
[SPEAKER_00]: They even gave you a Tesla to work there.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was really fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyway, I had to move out because I wanted to do more.
[SPEAKER_00]: At the time, blockchain was starting to become a thing because it was a bull run year, so I started to go to conferences, virtual reality, metaverse, and I just wanted to explore and see what's out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I even worked in two different projects, was temporary, but still related to blockchain.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then reality came in and I had to actually find a job who would give me a visa in the Netherlands.
[SPEAKER_00]: So then I came back to work in a company who could actually give me a visa.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that was my last engagement in the Netherlands, which is called NextGear.
[SPEAKER_00]: So then I started to create the data platform out of the blue, just like from scratch, because we didn't have anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: for analytics and their growing seed.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they needed actually real information and also to implement some of the first AI implementations I did in a workplace for getting content moderation metadata from media that was in the platform and give back to the main platform so they could work with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it was a hybrid position.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was the first time I actually
[SPEAKER_00]: had to be a leader on the team.
[SPEAKER_00]: So there was another engineer who was under me and also a data analyst who was definitely not technical.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I was learning how to do this better over time, how to use AI on our personal
[SPEAKER_00]: workflows, I use open code and Chinese models and everything you can imagine, I go for them, I don't like to simply use cloud or that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I started to be the person who was helping the people in the company to use AI in a more interesting way or could be better.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not directly in the platform because everyone is afraid of AI and at the time, to be honest, agentic was not even a thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just maybe chains with link chains, some open AI requests, nothing more than that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so, yeah, at some point I actually got my permanent residency for the EU and I didn't need a visa anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so then that's where I actually move out to Portugal.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I do have friends living in Viseu, which is close to Porto.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not sure where exactly they go, but I went there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I moved my company there just to be able to provide invoices, kept on being a partner of this company.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then after some time, I actually went to Brazil, came back to Brazil just for some vacation, some enjoying the time and working remote simply because I could do it then.
[SPEAKER_00]: To be very honest, last year I actually met my wife, we got together and
[SPEAKER_00]: We are very happy.
[SPEAKER_00]: And she was already doing the whole Italian citizenship thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You met her in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, she lives in Sao Paulo.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I was here and we met on the Tinder app.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it was actually Bumble.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then we just got together very easily.
[SPEAKER_00]: So after some time, we realized that we both wanted to go to Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: She was getting her citizenship.
[SPEAKER_00]: in two months now in June and I already had my documents so we had the perfect plan to just go so we're planning this since February because she was laid off from her company so we decided to just do it so she's looking for jobs in the privacy engineering world and I'm looking for the AI engineering
[SPEAKER_00]: product, AI, there's all kinds of names nowadays, and that's why I'm here.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm talking to Samuel, which is the recruiter guy, he's really nice, and he introduced me to Dmitry first, and I had a really nice conversation, and it looks like that you guys have a lot of answers on
[SPEAKER_00]: how people should be doing this thing, but also a bunch of good problems, because, I mean, if you get to this level of problem, you're in a good place.
[SPEAKER_00]: I read about how you grew, you know, from last year to this year, and there's a lot of demands.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyway, it's interesting to imagine working
[SPEAKER_00]: in a kind of problem situation that you guys have, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I see, I see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool, thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, interesting journey, especially the fact that like, you know, you started as a psychologist and then like a software engineer and then you changed into kind of a data engineer and then now you're kind of
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I feel very happy, to be honest, because I know for sure, for a real fact, that psychology helped me a lot in my career in terms of engineering, because of communication, you know, talking to people, prioritizing, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I went to data, and software was all over the place.
[SPEAKER_00]: So now, software, data, and understanding psychology really is useful in this AI engineering, especially if we're talking about the deliverables, not just the code.
[SPEAKER_00]: So for me, I feel very fortunate in this sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: To be honest, I was surprised to hear even that you became, as a leader, as a team lead, tech lead, not so early, because I would expect that, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: where you know how to talk with people, it might be the good way to manage people, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because communication is the key in most cases.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: I believe this is because I at some point had to leave places because, you know, I wanted to find something that was more fitting for my demands.
[SPEAKER_00]: And because of the visa situation, sometimes if I have like three companies in front of me, only one of them I can actually consider.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now I don't have this problem anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's a bit more comfortable for me to choose.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I felt the same many times.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let me ask quite a few questions.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just like, you know, to me, to see, I wouldn't say your kind of knowledge.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's more about your observability on the market and how you see things and how you feel things and how you understand what's going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, probably nobody understands it, but still.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, I saw in your CV a lot of different, like,
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's call them keyboards, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I want to ask about them.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you have here one chain, one graph, let's start with those.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you have experience with working with one chain, one graph, what you did when you use it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's definitely easier to just use one chain because it has most of the primitives you need to create some kind of a workflow or chain, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But of course, Lengraph, you're more able to control the workflow in detail where it should go where and what kind of output you should have for each use case.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I mean, personally, I like to use a functional API instead of the graph API.
[SPEAKER_00]: This whole object creating graphs thing, it's not really my zone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_00]: Can you explain why?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's because it's less descriptive, you know, it's a bit more like, it's not so easy to understand the function of each component you're creating if you're just having all together into different, it's more about the format than actually the function.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, that's why I prefer the functional API better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: By the way, on this note,
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you feel and think about like AI, how it should work?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's a little bit kind of philosophic question, but still.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's take programming languages, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Go, Python, you name it, like C, Harp, whatever, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So they were created for the people, like for human beings, like to read, to write, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now we have AI that can generate the code, old code, codex, again, all of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they use those languages, but it feels that they don't need those languages to generate because they were created for the humans, not for the machines, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: But at the same time, codex or code, they can't generate like a bytecode directly, right, also.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you feel, what do you think,
[SPEAKER_01]: what is the best would be the way to kind of to AI to LLM to generate not generate but create a software and how we can kind of skip this like languages and get the result somehow like just I mean there is no right answer definitely no for sure and to be honest from all the questions that I've been going through and imagining and that's definitely a very clear one there because like we
[SPEAKER_00]: The languages are for us, that's for sure, but I do not have a better solution than what we do now.
[SPEAKER_00]: The way I think about it is that at this point not only we can use the AI to improve how we do stuff and skip completely the let me type a function kind of situation,
[SPEAKER_00]: is that we actually have to be responsible for what's doing and actually know what's happening out there because we cannot trust the black box.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's going to create a binary, even if it could create a binary, and I know what it's going to be doing, I cannot really follow up and be able to improve from there.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think that's a language problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, psychology, we have the same.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have a thinking on your mind and you probably look outside because you're trying to formulate this into some phrase.
[SPEAKER_00]: But when you use language to portray it, you could use Bulgarian, Portuguese, English.
[SPEAKER_00]: you're always going to make it incomplete because you're going to put it into a shape and that's going to be a limited shape.
[SPEAKER_00]: All languages are limited, you know, there's some guys who used to say that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the way I see it is like, okay, if we still depend on us to be able to maintain and improve and go forward from the current state,
[SPEAKER_00]: We need to use some kind of technology, but of course, maybe the best solution is to use the technology that we happen to have more data for training.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's one way to see it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe TypeScript, because they don't know how to write in Go or Dart, but they do know a lot of TypeScript and Python.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's my point of view at this moment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I see I see I mean like to be honest like Python was created as a as a language for Kind of for the education as I remember right for the schools.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they're on the programming Yeah, and then somehow it became like it's the one of the main language, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah world
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, some would say that we can use Rust because it's never going to let you do dumb stuff and it's not going to build and compile unless it's perfect, but I don't think that's the way to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say maybe we should use the language that has less syntax to optimize on the token base.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, to get the same result with the less kind of words.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, let's go for COBOL then.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, sorry for this question, just like I was curious to hear how you think about this kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so we spoke about OpenCLO.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you tried it, like, EPS, a pair of your experience?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've tried it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Personally, I'm waiting for further releases.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually am more inclined to use Hermes Agent because maybe it's an evolution from it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, it's not the same.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the fact that
[SPEAKER_00]: OpenCloud is based on Pi, which is a very open framework for creating codee agents.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's on my list to go through Pi and be able to do something about it, but the problem is that
[SPEAKER_00]: AI is very creative when it doesn't work the way, so if it tries to go to the way A, it doesn't work and B doesn't work, it's always trying to be creative, it's not really thinking about the constraints all the time, there is no deterministic
[SPEAKER_00]: a guardrail by itself you can put it around it but it's not so for instance you'd say don't use the you know the edit tool okay great but then it's going to create some kind of a python inline and this python is going to override something and you feel okay now but then I can use virtual virtual space virtual mounts and then I there's not even a permission to write there right but then it's going to
[SPEAKER_00]: There's always something that you can do.
[SPEAKER_00]: And when you see you're just creating a whole huge software, it seems you should don't let the AI do what you're asking them to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's really complex on how you're actually going to let an AI do so much and believe it's going to work by itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I have a sandbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right, great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then you're already creating more hardware and solutions for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I like how it does, but if you don't have a specific workflow or specific workflows defined, you also should not have so much of a risk.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's very different from Phenom, of course, because you have a lot of risks going on and there is this difference between
[SPEAKER_00]: You have a backward AI or a forward AI where backward you just saw what happened in the past and say, this is something great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: You just gave a nice insight on something that is in the past.
[SPEAKER_00]: But if you're going to create like a tax filing for an entrepreneur person, then you're going to create something that is going to commit into consequences, possibly.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you get to this level of committing to something, you need to make sure that you
[SPEAKER_00]: not gonna like do what should not do without certainty and that's a big question.
[SPEAKER_00]: The problem is that OpenClojure is just gonna do more faster and if it does wrong it does more wrong things faster as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's nice for testing for prototyping and trying to understand how you can do it but it's not in the current state something that you can trust and yeah for companies that's really big as we we know.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's my view.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so I do agree with you overall, but at the same time, like as you said, harnesses, like AI harness, it's kind of a new thing completely and only because of the open core.
[SPEAKER_01]: it became a thing, right, because before, I mean, a few people were speaking about this, like, and, you know, using this, but now hardness is kind of almost a standard on the market, right, to go full.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, yeah, it's one way of understanding.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's, again, us trying to put this capability into our heads and with our language.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, of course, Harm is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I use OpenCode, for instance.
[SPEAKER_00]: I customize it a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have, like, this council and gods of, you know, there's a whole simplification of complexity that I try to use in different contexts.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's really cool and helped me to, you know, keep on the right direction.
[SPEAKER_00]: most of the times, but that's another concept that is still evolving.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I don't think that is the solution.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's just like another insight we should use in order to keep on going there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some year ago, someone would say that RUG is everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, we know that RUG is not everything.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have graph RUG now, but that's not great for many things, even though it's greater to other use cases.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, that's how I look at it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I need to open the door for the...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay, feel free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, so, yeah, interesting that you said about the rug, I just wanted to ask you, do you know who is Carpati?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, the auto-research guy, and he's publishing a bunch of stuff that everyone is trying to follow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah and interesting that like he always trying to break the market and like you know to bring something quite crazy and like to everyone to kind of discuss and hype around this and the the recent thing that he posted as I remember was about the rack and specifically that like he said that the rack kind of his approach is broken because like every time when you try to receive something
[SPEAKER_01]: It kind of starts from like again and again to the same thing, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he came up with the approach when you use Rack.
[SPEAKER_01]: together with the Wiki-style, Harness-style kind of approach.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of interesting, because I didn't dig in deeper into this topic.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it reminds me that, yes, this kind of approach that people will start using it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I saw that in 48 hours, the number of stars kind of grew super fast.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why it might be a sink at home, it might be just a hide around.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you seen this website here?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a good example.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're already doing this for some time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess it's kind of the same way.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a continuous process over your...
[SPEAKER_00]: work because your code base, as an example, is going to change from day to day depending on your amount of work.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they just do anything related to a repository.
[SPEAKER_00]: They explain stuff in a way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, you can change if you have your own.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can customize the way it's going to group information.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they're already doing this.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's an interesting concept, but it's already there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And to be honest, I think... Go on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go ahead, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm saying that the Karapati effect, I like to follow because he was really good at simplifying things.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the way I see his way of doing it, like, hey, this is not complex.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just creating something that is going to, you know, think outside the box or simply not repeat what's already done and to assume that this is the correct way.
[SPEAKER_00]: And a lot of companies are probably already doing the same thing that he created.
[SPEAKER_00]: but they are not calling this something or not selling or not posting just because it's their own internal research, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I guess we're all doing that somehow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this is the way, like you said it, like he's a researcher, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And his job is basically to research and kind of be open-minded and see what are the other way to do the same job and then kind of emphasize or even like, you know, influence because he's an influencer, definitely, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And influence people around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, so let's imagine that you need to create a new agent for operation, optimization, some kind of process, it does matter.
[SPEAKER_01]: How do you decide on the approach?
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you kind of
[SPEAKER_01]: Share your way of thinking like how you decide on the technology on the stack on the approach on there You go like a harness like blanks me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went chain one graph something or completely different story.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know okay, well I in terms of
[SPEAKER_00]: components, like in terms of implementation components, I like to separate what is a super optimizable component.
[SPEAKER_00]: One example is a prompt.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, there is no correct way to prompt something different from the other prompting, but definitely if you do a different prompting, you're going to get a different result.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's kind of like, OK, it just has to be better, and I have to observe and try different things forever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just have to do this nonstop.
[SPEAKER_00]: So recently, I found this.
[SPEAKER_00]: A month ago, I found this library called DSBY, which is a continuous prompting technique.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can send you.
[SPEAKER_00]: that is basically instead of creating like a string prompt which is as you can you can agree with me that it's very Stone Age and just write a big text and that's going to be the direction for your AI for your bigger workflow you actually create a signature where you say your expectations you can create metrics on top of this expectation just using normal evaluations but directly on the system
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's going to create like a loop.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of the auto researcher from Karpaty, where you're just going to simply improve.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, him, I guess, like, you know, because you're right, he was like auto researching something here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but of course, this is very specific for the prompt, so you're just going to be able to throw different possibilities.
[SPEAKER_00]: For instance, if I'm going to do a prompt for like, open the door, I'm going to try, hey, please open the door, here, pull the door, or, you know, kinds of door related stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: But this thing is going to use the AI capability to not think like a human and go many directions, just like, imagine you're a cow, then open the door.
[SPEAKER_00]: And maybe this is going to be better than just open the door, and you're never going to know that if you don't try.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the AI using the whole deterministic multiplication of options from the SPI, you can actually do this.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you don't have to trust good science, because that's the limitation.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are the bottleneck.
[SPEAKER_00]: we're going to decide judgment stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the SPI is a good example where there is a component that I can isolate from all the rest of the problem and simply say, I can fully optimize forever this prompt until it becomes something better and better and better.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's already going to do a big part of the job.
[SPEAKER_00]: The second separation I do is actually what's on workflow and what's agentic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because a workflow, you should probably do something very specific when it comes to, for instance, in your case, there is an expense and I need to categorize this expense.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe there is some specific criteria that I have to follow in order to get there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in this part,
[SPEAKER_00]: I like to use what I call this mental model of zoom in, zoom out.
[SPEAKER_00]: So if I tell you, hey, please get me a good recommendation for a movie and you're just going to black box some idea and give me a solution.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I say, maybe it's a good, maybe it's not, but I want to make sure it's always going to be good for everyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I need to zoom in.
[SPEAKER_00]: I open this request and say, how do I actually answer this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Then you have, oh,
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to get at least two preferences and topics the person likes, and you also need to get something that people fear.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you define some specific internal joints you need to define, and then as much as you can get deterministic on these pieces,
[SPEAKER_00]: the better because you're going to be able to control those pieces in a deterministic skeleton and so the more you can do this the better and you'll just leave the messy judgment extraction stuff to the AI because it's really good but the smaller the better so I like to think of those dimensions you know super optimization of components when it's possible and then differentiation between well-defined workflows
[SPEAKER_00]: and also the not so well-defined agents, agentic flows, and then the whole zoom in, zoom out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because if you're going to look at the technical problem in Phenom and try to see where it's failing, why it's failing, why it's not consistent results, then you need to zoom in to the joints and see if you're just leaving to the AI to give you a black box solution.
[SPEAKER_00]: and to remove that of course, and the zoom out is really good for you to understand, okay, then I can do this magical AI thingy here with this document, how can I fit this into my platform?
[SPEAKER_00]: How can I make this to generate value for the user and of course for the company?
[SPEAKER_00]: then I use this kind of like a solar system to the star, to the planets kind of like zooming in, zooming out way to identify where's the problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting that you have analogy for almost everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have kind of like a mental framework for every step.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do have, I think that's from psychology because I needed to do some psycho education during therapy as well, people to understand differences of stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, long story, but the thing is I try to understand, because of course you can decompose the task
[SPEAKER_00]: forever and then it's going to be too, you know, too much decomposed, not necessary maybe, but if you can actually decompose this to a level that you can control the process, you can actually trust AI because it's going to have 100% success rates on something that is very controllable instead of having 75% in the whole workflow at once, which is a bit dumb, of course, as a comparison.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so that's how I try to
[SPEAKER_00]: break this problem into how to approach it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So from the product value to the company, to the user, going directly to the joints that I say, and leaving this armor around the intelligence of the AI.
[SPEAKER_00]: and decomposing between different components and optimizing where it's possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's also how I was studying a bit what Dimitri told me about your team separation.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not sure if you're now more on the embed version or the centralized versions, if you have everything in the team or... We're kind of like in the middle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, like overall, like he said, I guess, like about the functions and domains, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is how we work usually.
[SPEAKER_01]: in case with AI team it's a little bit different we do have a few people who are kind of embedded into the domains but at the same time we have people who are not kind of connected and they just jump from project to project because the AI team not big to be honest because and interesting fact maybe it's a weird situation but we
[SPEAKER_01]: we think different about AI and ML, machine learning.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for us, it's kind of completely different stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we have ML team, and we have AI team.
[SPEAKER_01]: And ML team, it's about just a classic applied ML, such as credit score, I don't know, like risk scoring, like this kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And my team is mostly focusing on this kind of utilizing LLMs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, most of them are ML engineers from the past experience.
[SPEAKER_01]: But again, today, nowadays, I don't think you have to be a ML engineer to work
[SPEAKER_01]: more.
[SPEAKER_01]: And AI, kind of working with AI, is the same as any others of engineering.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have different APIs, different JSONs to pass from left to right or right to left.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, of course, the most important is the way how you think about the patterns, the architecture, and the knowledge that you understand the market, you understand the existing frameworks, approaches, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the way how I see it.
[SPEAKER_00]: My perception is that nowadays when someone says AI engineer, of course if you remove the ML to simplify because it's a very big difference, I never know exactly if they're thinking more on the
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to understand how to extract value from a possible integration I can do using AI, or if you want me to actually create the integrations, technically speaking, because both are important, but they are talking about very different problems.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like to imagine that I can be in the middle because of my personal upbringing, but I never know exactly where the companies are in maturity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can you elaborate on this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, just to make sure that I kind of understand what you mean here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because if I'm talking about an AI engineer, especially if it's coming from a central AI team, which is thinking about, you know, research that is coming up nowadays, but also someone who's going to be embedded on domain teams, we're not thinking about Kapati at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: then how to translate from one place to the other is a big part of the work and also not to be completely, you know, deluded by the fact that, oh, we could do something really cool here with the technology, it's going to sound amazing, but it's not going to be translated into some kind of product value or even it's going to be a product value, but not for the company, not for the user.
[SPEAKER_00]: it's a complex problem that you probably have a lot of experience on the product size, on the product level, but now people are leaving the code and thinking about product and how to use AI for something useful and...
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, tell me please, like, you're kind of... it is interesting perspective to give us, like, because you're saying that, like, if you're going to be as a part of domain embedded, like, then you
[SPEAKER_01]: you are not going to kind of research or see those stuff, cool stuff, let's call it this way, and instead you're just going to be focused on the product, on the feature, on delivery.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, your colleagues, your colleagues, the domain people, let's say the finance people, you know, and the finance people are working to find out where they are, they are using the workflows, but they are not sure how to transform the whole process.
[SPEAKER_00]: with an AI layer in a useful way and you're bringing this mindset, this capability of looking and how you can do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you have to be the translator between the central AI, who are only talking about possibilities and the philosophy that we're talking right now, and bring that into reasonable ways of understanding to the domain people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exact solutions.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's an interesting work.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the thing, like, I don't really kind of separate those two stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to be honest, for me, it's like one after another.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's like a cycle.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as you said, it's like we are not in the middle.
[SPEAKER_01]: doing exactly both things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I don't believe that, like, you know, implementing some, creating a process, optimizing, it's not like finance team, as you said, or like other domains came to us saying what to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's usually us come to them, say, hey, you need to change the process.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we do have a lot of, I would say, influence on other teams, domains, the whole company, I would say.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we literally can come to any team and say, you are doing it wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to do it this way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is this a mandate?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I can imagine that you're going to have some, you know, legacy knowledge on the team and people are not going to know exactly how to adopt this, so the adoption rate is going to drop if you just mandate people to use it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not mandatory, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of, this is the trick moment, so we need to be kind of
[SPEAKER_01]: As influencers, like eternal influencers.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's why we have, as I said, we have the first one, we call it like operation excellence.
[SPEAKER_01]: The second thing, the stream.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have the AI inside the product, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And the third thing, we call it like AI adoption.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we have a dedicated person whose job, her job only one, is to influence the whole company and transform the company into the AI
[SPEAKER_01]: AI-first approach.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she's doing a lot of different stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: For example, two weeks ago we had a hackathon in Chernobyl.
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole company was working on different projects, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it was a few conditions that you can use only AI tools and it should be somehow related to AI.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are doing a lot of different workshops, internal, external.
[SPEAKER_01]: We buy a lot of different tools and stuff for the engineering team, for the product team.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I don't know, the way how they're code, code even, like, using.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, like, some of the people are early adopters, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: They use those, like, code, code, et cetera, codex.
[SPEAKER_01]: But some of the engineers, they're not using.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't use, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: They haven't used.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is the way, like, we are working with, together with the beta
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say, kind of bring it as a process to the whole engineering team, but then after, beyond the engineering team, to make it as a kind of like a tool for everyone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because again, cold code is hardness, basically, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Similar to open code or other stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, sorry, we are running out of time, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's make it... You have 10 more minutes?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_00]: Feel free.
[SPEAKER_01]: cool just to finish uh so um what i wanted to ask you like hearing from me all this stuff like so again i'm looking for somebody who uh open-minded
[SPEAKER_01]: brave enough to kind of to think differently and see differently but at the same time with a good knowledge on what to do and how to do so it's like kind of not just thinking about this stuff but executed and executed fast and when I say fast what I mean because you know people started to use the quote-unquote codecs
[SPEAKER_01]: work faster.
[SPEAKER_01]: The question is why.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sometimes the opposite.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, sometimes the opposite.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's why, like, for me it's important, like, I want to have a small team.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to have, like, a big team.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I do believe that, like, it's better to have a small team with good salaries, with good tools, with good toys to play with.
[SPEAKER_01]: than to have like you know hundreds of people yeah who are just average um so that's why like this this is who i'm looking for um um yeah is it is it something that like kind of do you feel here much
[SPEAKER_00]: I do.
[SPEAKER_00]: Simple answer.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the reason why is because, I mean, you can look at my profile and I can tell my story forever if that would be the case.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is, I was always a generalist person and then I became a generalist engineer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I like to bring different topics into the conversation, even when it's not necessarily engineering, because I think they are relevant.
[SPEAKER_00]: For instance, I mentioned to you about the
[SPEAKER_00]: this Lacanian or Freudian way to see the language as a limiting tool, and that actually is very fitting when we talk about LLMs and workflows, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: I usually do this experiment where if I want to create a business in this world as capitalists, how do I think in a different model without using the normal capitalist way?
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's really hard because we've done this forever and we just don't know what the right to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: So now that people have, let's say, a magic wand that they can do something the software could not before, you just have to do exactly that.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to imagine how you could offer something that is valuable, but it was never imagined to be possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: But now it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: So how do you, with something that is amazingly possible, you can create something
[SPEAKER_00]: that people are going to desire and they are going to desire a lot of things, but then you cannot fail because of issues.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think that's a huge problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like it because it's related to the things that get me out of bed in the night and looking to research, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I know that I have this discipline to not forget about what's missing when you're going to create something that works all the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I do, and those are the reasons, but of course if you have a way to evaluate from your side, of course, I would be happy to know and follow up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just one more question here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think you can influence people?
[SPEAKER_00]: That I can influence people?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I've been doing this for my career the whole time.
[SPEAKER_00]: For instance, a good example is my first job, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just got there to do the version 2 of the frontend application.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I realized that these web scrapers were running as a Java monster.
[SPEAKER_00]: monorepo situation and then I was like why don't you use and I was thinking why don't we use this microservice I'm like maybe I don't understand enough and then after some time I started to go through this idea and asking people going small and understanding the concept the context and at some point I said okay maybe we should do this and I actually owned the idea to say I know it's gonna work and then I created this multi container solution using AWS CCS and lately also Lambda for small transformations
[SPEAKER_00]: And it actually worked a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, you know, it was nice to see that it was launched.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I went through the company because of my opinions.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was not even the person implementing all the technology because I was still a junior.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, I like to imagine that I am very influenceable because I like to understand
[SPEAKER_00]: what people are pain are feeling the pain so I know where to go to you know try to address that with real solution not just keep on my own avenue without listening to others so this listening is my superpower I think and the last question is like um yeah so as you know like we do have like different people from different countries etc but like this is I would say it's our legacy that like most of the engineering team are
[SPEAKER_01]: from Russia originally.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't live in Russia, but they're Russian.
[SPEAKER_01]: And how do you feel about that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, not from the kind of... Yeah, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I just need to open the door for the dog.
[SPEAKER_01]: He just, you know, like, comes in, comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, so my point here is that... Do you feel comfortable kind of working with the
[SPEAKER_01]: like maybe you had like our experience working with the Russian developers and especially the moment that like I mean at some point not all of them not inside my team but like all of the some of them they might be not so good in communication etc and this is kind of it's not kind of a red flag but still I
[SPEAKER_01]: I decided to ask because, you know, just to manage expectations, I would say.
[SPEAKER_01]: They might be direct, but not because they kind of...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just the way how they think.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a mindset, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, two things.
[SPEAKER_00]: First, I worked for seven years in the Dutch market.
[SPEAKER_00]: So the Dutch are also very direct and they're not very fluffy, the way they say.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's already my personal preference, to be honest, and also experience.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the second is that in terms of communication skills, I, without being harsh or anything, just I like to be the bigger person in the room.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that is going to get me a good position
[SPEAKER_00]: because it's not about who is you know saying louder it's actually who is bringing some way to go forward and i'm usually capable to be that person so that's great for me uh and i know how to understand limits i know people are not doing stuff because they're trying to hurt you uh the whole psychology again so yeah that's not a problem for me i like your that you're so confident anyway cool uh so uh
[SPEAKER_01]: I would propose the following.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it would be great if you can find a time when you can speak with one of the AI engineers, our lead AI engineer, who can kind of, let's say, check with your technical side.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I am kind of a little bit technical, but I'm not super technical.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it would be great to kind of evaluate this stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: um and then yeah if everything would go good from your side from our side then we can do like i don't know like a next step and then see how it will go okay yeah uh do you know how usually goes like a technical interview i guess and then uh some other usually it's like a technical interview and then that's it i guess like a decision and if you want to kind of meet a team before or meet somebody
[SPEAKER_01]: how it usually goes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because, like, in your case, I don't know, you spoke with Dmitry, have you with somebody else?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_01]: No?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Usually it's like a recruiter, then me, then technical interview, then decision, and then some random stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then technical interview, I want to be creative, like, every time we change some stuff there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not just, like, going to be questions and answers.
[SPEAKER_01]: but i'm gonna make it like i don't know something great i have no idea what it's going to be if there's kind of but we will come up with something interesting nice cool thank you thank you for the time i know we went through and uh it was really nice conversation yeah thank you very much uh so uh then we have a few contacts uh i don't know i need to check because i guess somebody's uh somebody's okay i'm gonna check with me three
[SPEAKER_01]: because I have no idea where you come from.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, thank you very much, have a nice day!